(Howard:)Yeah, that one.
(Howard:)You can modify it
to calculate our chances of having sex...
(Howard:)...by changing the formula
to use single women in Los Angeles...
(Howard:)...those who might find us attractive...
(Howard:)...and what I call
The Wolowitz Coefficient.
- The Wolowitz Coefficient?
- Neediness times dress-size squared.
In crunching the numbers, I come up with a
conservative 5812 potential sex partners...
(Howard:)...within a 40-mile radius.
(Leonard:)You're joking.
(Howard:)I'm a horny engineer, Leonard.
(Howard:)I never joke about math or sex.
(Raj:)Well, what are we waiting for?
Let's bounce, bitches.
Oh, you're right.
It's Anything Can Happen Thursday.
(Leonard:)Let's hit the clubs
and meet hot women.
(Raj:)Here we go. Lock up your daughters.
We're gonna hit it and quit it.
(Leonard:)Or we could finish eating
and go to the comic book store.
(Raj:)Also a good plan.
(Howard:)But next Anything Can Happen Thursday,
we're going to a bar.
- Oh, absolutely.
- You heard that, Ladies' Night ladies?
(Raj:)We're eventually coming for you.
(Sheldon:)Fascinating.